No matter what happened in our childhood,
we recognize our patterns and we can reprogram them.
I will not erase your story,
but I will desensitize some traumas, some sensations,
and together we co-create a
different reality through reprogramming
techniques and inner child hypnosis,
and we place you in different
situations, where the outcomes are
different, where the sensations are different,
forming new neural synapses, forming a different chemistry.
Then we keep strengthening that path, and we
change our inner reality and our outer reality.
We change our sense of self-confidence,
we change the way we feel about our own worth,
we change what we expect from
a relationship, our relationship with money.
And then everything around us starts to change.